https://www.sfccapital.com/privacy

Disclaimer
Please note, company introductions through SFC Capital Ltd ('SFC') are only suitable for ‘High Net Worth Individuals’, or ‘Sophisticated Investors’ as defined by the Financial Services & Markets Act 2000 (FSMA) who are familiar with and willing to accept the high risk associated with private investments. Any investor requesting to contact a company through SFC Capital does so at his/her own risk and is solely responsible for conducting any legal, accounting or due diligence review. There has been no investigation to the accuracy of any information or terms contained herein and we strongly suggest that you seek advice from a person authorised under the FSMA who specialises in advising on investments of this kind prior to commencement of any potential transaction. All content provided by SFC Capital is strictly for informational purpose only and does not constitute business, financial, investment, hedging, trading, legal, regulatory, tax or accounting advice or services. SFC Capital is an appointed representative of SFC Capital Partners Ltd which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (‘FCA’) in the United Kingdom (FRN 736284). This website is intended for professional investors only; any reproduction of this information, in whole, or part, is prohibited. SFC Capital does not sell or offer to sell any securities and no information provided by SFC Capital is intended to constitute or to be interpreted as any such offer. SFC Capital simply provides an introductory service where potential partners of all sorts can meet.The SFC Angel Fund is managed by SFC Capital Partners Ltd (‘SFCCP’) which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority in the United Kingdom, firm reference number 736284. Information on the Fund is intended for professional investors only; any reproduction of this information, in whole, or part, is prohibited. The content is for information purposes only and should not be used or considered as an offer or solicitation to purchase or sell the securities mentioned herein. The SFC Angel Fund (the ‘SFC Fund’ or the ‘Fund’) is defined as an ‘unregulated collective investment scheme’ (‘UCIS’) and the promotion of a UCIS either within the UK or from the UK is severely restricted by statute. Consequently, this document is only directed at professional clients and eligible counterparties as defined by the FCA and also to persons of a kind to whom the Fund may lawfully be promoted by an authorised person by virtue of Section 238(5) of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 and COBS 4.12.4R. Any decision by an investor to buy shares in a fund must be made solely on the basis of the information and terms contained within the Fund’s offering memorandum. Investment in the Fund is made entirely at the investor’s own risk and professional advice should be sought in case of doubt.SFC Capital Partners Ltd (‘SFC’) is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (‘FCA’) in the United Kingdom, firm reference number 736284. This document is intended for professional investors only; any reproduction of this information, in whole, or part, is prohibited.
The content is for information purposes only and should not be used or considered as an offer or solicitation to purchase or sell the securities mentioned herein. The SFC Angel Fund (the ‘SFC Fund’ or the ‘Fund’) is defined as an ‘unregulated collective investment scheme’ (‘UCIS’) and the promotion of a UCIS either within the UK or from the UK is severely restricted by statute.
Consequently, this document is only directed at professional clients and eligible counterparties as defined by the FCA and also to persons of a kind to whom the Fund may lawfully be promoted by an authorised person by virtue of Section 238(5) of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 and COBS 4.12.4R.The SFC Angel Fund is managed by SFC Capital Partners Ltd (‘SFCCP’) which is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority in the United Kingdom, firm reference number 736284. Information on the Fund is intended for professional investors only; any reproduction of this information, in whole, or part, is prohibited. The content is for information purposes only and should not be used or considered as an offer or solicitation to purchase or sell the securities mentioned herein. The SFC Angel Fund (the ‘SFC Fund’ or the ‘Fund’) is defined as an ‘unregulated collective investment scheme’ (‘UCIS’) and the promotion of a UCIS either within the UK or from the UK is severely restricted by statute. Consequently, this document is only directed at professional clients and eligible counterparties as defined by the FCA and also to persons of a kind to whom the Fund may lawfully be promoted by an authorised person by virtue of Section 238(5) of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 and COBS 4.12.4R. Any decision by an investor to buy shares in a fund must be made solely on the basis of the information and terms contained within the Fund’s offering memorandum. Investment in the Fund is made entirely at the investor’s own risk and professional advice should be sought in case of doubt.The SFC Angel Fund is an SEIS/EIS fund which raises money for early-stage businesses by investing in SEIS and EIS eligible ventures with the aim of returning a profit for investors in the fund. Investment in early-stage companies involves risks such as illiquidity, lack of dividends, loss of investment and dilution. Investment in SEIS/EIS funds should be considered as part of a diversified portfolio. The availability of tax relief depends on individual circumstances and may change in the future. The availability of tax relief depends on the company invested in maintaining its SEIS/EIS qualifying status. There is no assurance that the investment objectives of any investment product will be achieved or that the strategies and methods described herein will be successful. Past performance is not necessarily a guide to future performance and the value of an investment may go down as well as up. Investors may not get back the full amount invested. No warranties or representations of any kind are expressed or implied on this website.
I Accept The Terms
Login
Home
Raise
Invest
Our Portfolio
About Us
Blog
Raise
Invest
Privacy Policy
Updated in May 2018 and compliant with GDPR rules
Introduction
The Startup Funding Group of Companies (the "Organisation") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Policy explains how your personal information is processed by the Organisation, including any affiliates listed in the Data Controllers and Contact section below (hereinafter also collectively referred to as "us", or "we").This Policy covers personal information relating to you that we may collect through any medium, including specifically in relation to the investment services we provide to you, via our partners and service providers, or through our website. This policy describes how you can access and make certain choices about how we use your personal information.
Your personal information that we may collect
We may collect and process data the below listed information with respect to persons connected with the Angel networking and investment services that we provide. As well as collecting personal data from our clients, we may also process personal data about relevant persons connected with the investment services, for example investors in our funds, co-investors, directors of investee startup companies, etc.We may collect this information from a number of sources, including directly from you, via our affiliates, delegates, partners, service providers, professional advisors, or third-party entities with whom we undertake due diligence checks upon you. In doing so, we will ensure that the information we collect is proportionate to our stated purposes.Where relevant, we may collect and process personal information related to persons related to you. In such circumstances, it is your responsibility to ensure you have permission from that third-party for us to collect their information and you remain responsible for ensuring that the third-party understands how their information is being used.Individuals connected with our investment servicesWe may collect and process your personal details, including your name, address, email and telephone/fax numbers, date of birth, nationality; employment details, including your employers name, your position or title and your corporate contact details; information on your financial circumstances, including your profession, income, assets and liabilities, as well as sensitive and/or criminal data as part of our standard due diligence process.Individuals connected with our partners and service providersWe may collect and process your contact information, including your name, address, position, email and telephone/fax numbers; financial details, including relevant details for invoicing and billing; and KYC documentation, if and where required under relevant Anti-Money Laundering or Counter Terrorism Financing ("AML/CTF") legislation.Individuals connected with our websiteWe may collect and process your personal details, including your name, address, email and telephone/fax numbers, as well as your login identification and password details; and technical information, including your IP address, browser information, and details relating to your visit behaviour on our website. Further details are provided under our &#39Cookie Policy' heading below.
Our legal bases and purpose for holding your personal information
Unless specifically stated otherwise in a Privacy Notice provided to you, we use your personal information in the following ways and based upon the following lawful bases:Individuals connected with our investment servicesIn order to achieve our legitimate interests. In doing so, we ensure that:your rights and interests are considered and protected and there is a minimal privacy impact upon you;we are able to demonstrate that we use your data in a proportionate manner and you would not likely be surprised or likely to object to our usage;we can lawfully disclose personal data to a third-parties where we can demonstrate that this disclosure is justified;To comply with our legal or regulatory obligations. For instance, under the UK Financial Conduct Authority Conduct of Business rules and/or relevant AML/CTF legislation;Based upon reasons of substantial public interest; andWhere your personal information is public information by your own actions.Individuals connected with our partners and service providersIn order to fulfil our contractual obligations to you in order to facilitate the provision of goods or services. This includes where you have asked us to do something before entering into a contract, for example to provide a quote;To comply with our legal or regulatory obligations. For instance, under relevant AML/CTF legislation;Based upon reasons of substantial public interest; andWhere your personal information is public information by your own actions.Individuals connected with our websiteIn order to achieve our legitimate interests. This may include electronic communications between us; the provision of investment information to you; details in order for us to manage and improve our website; for us obtaining and recording details relating to your visit behaviour on our website;To comply with our legal or regulatory obligations. For instance, under relevant AML/CTF legislation;Based upon reasons of substantial public interest; andWhere your personal information is public information by your own actions.
When we may disclose your personal information
We may disclose your personal information with the following category of recipients, and based upon the legal bases and purposes set-out above:Our affiliates, including where relevant third-party investment funds that we either manage or advise.Our partners and service providers, including service providers appointed by the third-party investment funds that we either manage or advise and including our appointed representatives where appropriate;Any law enforcement, court, regulator or other government authority in order for us to comply with a legal obligation laid down by UK or EU law. This includes the provision of information relating to any affiliate of the Organisation.A prospective buyer of our business, including where we intend to sell part of our business or merge with another third-party.
How and where we store your personal information
We store your physically held personal information in our UK offices. Whereas we store your electronically held personal information on third party backed up servers that might not be located in EU. We understand that we have to ensure that service providers do comply with GDPR requirements.We take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information; however, where you choose to transmit your personal data to us via the internet, we do not guarantee the security of the personal information transmitted and therefore any transmission is at your own risk.We may transfer your personal information to our affiliates, partners or service providers that are based outside of the European Economic Area. In such circumstances, we will ensure that your personal information is adequately protected to European Commission approved standards.
Your rights as a Data subject
In certain circumstances, in relation to your data, you have:the right to be informed,the right of access,the right to rectification,the right to erasure,the right to restrict processing,the right to data portability,the right to object, andrights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.Further details of your rights can be found at the ICO website, however, please note that your rights are subject to our overarching legal responsibilities:https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact the relevant data controller (listed below).
How long we retain your personal information
We reserve the right to retain your personal information for as long as we reasonably believe it to be necessary in order to facilitate our legitimate interests, in order for us to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, where based upon reasons of substantial public interest, or where your personal information remains public information by your own actions. For further information, please contact the relevant data controller (listed below).
Our responsibilities when we make changes to our Privacy Policy
We may make changes to our Privacy Policy at any time and may do so without expressly notifying you of these changes. However, should the legal bases or purpose for processing your personal information changes then we shall expressly notify you.
Our Data Controllers and how to contact us
Questions or individual data requests relating to this Policy should be addressed to the relevant data controller. For the purpose of the data protection legislation, the relevant data controllers are:
Data Controller
Responsible for
SFC Capital Partners Ltd
Co registration no: 09226119
1-6 SPEEDY PLACE
CROMER STREET
LONDON
ENGLAND
GDPR contact person: Marguerite Crossfield
Investment and business administration activities related to our regulated activities. Principal firm to Appointed Representatives.
SFC Ltd
Co registration no: 08191242
1-6 SPEEDY PLACE
CROMER STREET
LONDON
ENGLAND
WC1H 8BU
GDPR contact person: Angelika Burawska
Angel networking entity (Appointed Representative).
Bennet Brooks
Co registration no: 02648803
St. George's Court
Winnington Avenue
Northwich
CW8 4EE
ichiban@bennettbrooks.co.uk
0845 330 3200
Provision of delegated investment services by the Organisation.
Innvotec Limited
Co registration no: 02030086
Painters Hall
9 Little Trinity Lane
London
EC4V 2AD
info@innvotec.co.uk
+44 (0) 207 630 6990
Investment and business administration activities related to our regulated activities.
Enterprise Investment Partners
Co registration no: OC357090
1-6 SPEEDY PLACE
CROMER STREET
LONDON
ENGLAND
WC1H 8BU
info@enterprise-ip.com
+ 44 (0) 20 7843 0470
Investment and business administration activities related to our regulated activities.
Woodside Corporate Services
Co registration no: 06171085
4th Floor 50 Mark Lane,
London, EC3R 7QR
+44 (0) 44 02032162000
Investment and business administration activities related to our regulated activities.
Our Cookie Policy
A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user's computer by the user's web browser while the user is browsing. We only use cookies that are required for the essential operation of our website. These cookies are typically deleted from your device once the browsing session is terminated.You can choose to block cookies that we may deliver to your device through settings on your web-browser; however, in doing so you may not be able to access or utilise all aspects of our website.
